[
    {
        "question_text": "1929、有关腹膜的描述正确是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.只衬于腹、盆腔脏器的表面",
            "B.分为前、后两层",
            "C.前层又分为脏层和壁层",
            "D.为浆膜",
            "E.没有分泌和吸收功能"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 1
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1930、有关腹膜腔的错误描述是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.由腹膜的脏层和壁层围成",
            "B.与胸膜腔一样，男、女腹膜腔均为密闭、负压",
            "C.为一潜在性腔隙",
            "D.属腹膜内的浆膜腔",
            "E.内有少量浆液"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 2
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1931、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.空肠",
            "C.子宫",
            "D.胰",
            "E.升结肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 3
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1932、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.升结肠",
            "C.膀胱",
            "D.胃",
            "E.胆囊"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 4
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1933、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肾",
            "B.输尿管",
            "C.升结肠",
            "D.脾",
            "E.横结肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 5
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1934、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.子宫",
            "B.横结肠",
            "C.回肠",
            "D.肾",
            "E.胰"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 6
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1935、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠",
            "B.胃",
            "C.空肠",
            "D.子宫",
            "E.输尿管"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 7
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1936、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠",
            "B.胰",
            "C.子宫",
            "D.空肠",
            "E.乙状结肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 8
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1937、指出下列的错误描述（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.腹膜腔和腹腔是两个不同的概念",
            "B.腹膜腔位于腹腔内",
            "C.腹腔内脏器均位于腹膜腔内",
            "D.女性腹膜腔可间接和外界相通",
            "E.男性腹膜腔不和外界相通"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 9
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1938、肝十二韧带内重要结构排列是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.右前方为胆总管，左前方为肝门静脉，二者之间后方为肝固有动脉",
            "B.右前方为胆总管，左前方为肝固有动脉，二者之间后方为肝门静脉",
            "C.右前方为肝门静脉，左前方为肝固有动脉，二者之间后方为胆总管",
            "D.右前方为肝固有动脉，左前方为胆总管，二者之间后方为肝门静脉",
            "E.右前方为肝固有动脉，左前方为肝门静脉，二者之间后方为胆总管"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 10
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1939、指出有关网膜孔的错误描述（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为网膜囊与腹膜腔其余部分之间的唯一通道",
            "B.上界为肝尾状叶",
            "C.下界为十二指肠上部",
            "D.前界为横结肠系膜",
            "E.后界为覆盖于下腔静脉表面的腹膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 11
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1940、没有系膜的肠管是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.升结肠",
            "B.横结肠",
            "C.乙状结肠",
            "D.空肠",
            "E.阑尾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 12
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1941、不属于腹膜形成的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.镰状韧带",
            "B.冠状韧带",
            "C.肝圆韧带",
            "D.胃脾韧带",
            "E.脾肾韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 13
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1942、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.胃",
            "C.胰",
            "D.肛管",
            "E.尿道"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 14
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1943、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.胃",
            "C.胰",
            "D.肛管",
            "E.尿道"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 15
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1944、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.胃",
            "C.胰",
            "D.肛管",
            "E.尿道"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 16
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1945、属腹膜内位器官的是（ ）",
        "options": [
            "A.尿道",
            "B.空肠",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.阴道"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 17
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1946、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.尿道",
            "B.肾",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.阴道",
            "E.空肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 18
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1947、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.尿道",
            "B.肾",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.阴道",
            "E.空肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 19
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1948、脐静脉闭锁后的遗迹是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 20
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1949、内有胆总管的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 21
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1950、内有胰尾的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 22
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1951、位于脾下方的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 23
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1952、手术中确定空肠起始处标志的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 24
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1953、与网膜孔围成的有关韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 25
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1954、内有胃短血管的韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 26
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1955、内有胃左、右血管的韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 27
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1956、与膈相连的韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 28
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1957、为大网膜一部分的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 29
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1958、平卧位男性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 30
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1959、平卧位女性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 31
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1960、站立或坐位男性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 32
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1961、站立或坐位女性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 33
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1962、固定空、回肠的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 34
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1963、将腹膜腔划分为结肠上区和结肠下区的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 35
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1964、呈三角形，游离缘有血管的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 36
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1965、位于左髂窝内的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 37
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1929、有关腹膜的描述正确是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.只衬于腹、盆腔脏器的表面",
            "B.分为前、后两层",
            "C.前层又分为脏层和壁层",
            "D.为浆膜",
            "E.没有分泌和吸收功能"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 38
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1930、有关腹膜腔的错误描述是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.由腹膜的脏层和壁层围成",
            "B.与胸膜腔一样，男、女腹膜腔均为密闭、负压",
            "C.为一潜在性腔隙",
            "D.属腹膜内的浆膜腔",
            "E.内有少量浆液"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 39
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1931、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.空肠",
            "C.子宫",
            "D.胰",
            "E.升结肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 40
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1932、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.升结肠",
            "C.膀胱",
            "D.胃",
            "E.胆囊"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 41
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1933、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肾",
            "B.输尿管",
            "C.升结肠",
            "D.脾",
            "E.横结肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 42
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1934、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.子宫",
            "B.横结肠",
            "C.回肠",
            "D.肾",
            "E.胰"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 43
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1935、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠",
            "B.胃",
            "C.空肠",
            "D.子宫",
            "E.输尿管"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 44
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1936、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠",
            "B.胰",
            "C.子宫",
            "D.空肠",
            "E.乙状结肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 45
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1937、指出下列的错误描述（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.腹膜腔和腹腔是两个不同的概念",
            "B.腹膜腔位于腹腔内",
            "C.腹腔内脏器均位于腹膜腔内",
            "D.女性腹膜腔可间接和外界相通",
            "E.男性腹膜腔不和外界相通"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 46
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1938、肝十二韧带内重要结构排列是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.右前方为胆总管，左前方为肝门静脉，二者之间后方为肝固有动脉",
            "B.右前方为胆总管，左前方为肝固有动脉，二者之间后方为肝门静脉",
            "C.右前方为肝门静脉，左前方为肝固有动脉，二者之间后方为胆总管",
            "D.右前方为肝固有动脉，左前方为胆总管，二者之间后方为肝门静脉",
            "E.右前方为肝固有动脉，左前方为肝门静脉，二者之间后方为胆总管"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 47
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1939、指出有关网膜孔的错误描述（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为网膜囊与腹膜腔其余部分之间的唯一通道",
            "B.上界为肝尾状叶",
            "C.下界为十二指肠上部",
            "D.前界为横结肠系膜",
            "E.后界为覆盖于下腔静脉表面的腹膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 48
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1940、没有系膜的肠管是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.升结肠",
            "B.横结肠",
            "C.乙状结肠",
            "D.空肠",
            "E.阑尾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 49
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1941、不属于腹膜形成的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.镰状韧带",
            "B.冠状韧带",
            "C.肝圆韧带",
            "D.胃脾韧带",
            "E.脾肾韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 50
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1942、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.胃",
            "C.胰",
            "D.肛管",
            "E.尿道"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 51
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1943、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.胃",
            "C.胰",
            "D.肛管",
            "E.尿道"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 52
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1944、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.胃",
            "C.胰",
            "D.肛管",
            "E.尿道"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 53
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1945、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.尿道",
            "B.肾",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.阴道",
            "E.空肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 54
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1946、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.尿道",
            "B.肾",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.阴道",
            "E.空肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 55
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1947、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.尿道",
            "B.肾",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.阴道",
            "E.空肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 56
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1948、脐静脉闭锁后的遗迹是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 57
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1949、内有胆总管的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 58
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1950、内有胰尾的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 59
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1951、位于脾下方的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 60
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1952、手术中确定空肠起始处标志的韧带是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝圆韧带",
            "B.膈结肠韧带",
            "C.十二指肠悬韧带韧带",
            "D.脾肾韧带",
            "E.肝十二指肠韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 61
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1953、与网膜孔围成的有关韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 62
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1954、内有胃短血管的韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 63
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1955、内有胃左、右血管的韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 64
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1956、与膈相连的韧带（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 65
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1957、为大网膜一部分的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝十二指肠韧带",
            "B.胃脾韧带",
            "C.胃结肠韧带",
            "D.冠状韧带",
            "E.肝胃韧带"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 66
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1958、平卧位男性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 67
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1959、平卧位女性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 68
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1960、站立或坐位男性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 69
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1961、站立或坐位女性腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝肾隐窝",
            "B.直肠子宫陷凹",
            "C.直肠膀胱陷凹",
            "D.膀胱子宫陷凹",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 70
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1962、固定空、回肠的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 71
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1963、将腹膜腔划分为结肠上区和结肠下区的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 72
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1964、呈三角形，游离缘有血管的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 73
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1965、位于左髂窝内的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠系膜",
            "B.肠系膜",
            "C.阑尾系膜",
            "D.乙状结肠系膜",
            "E.子宫系膜"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 74
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1966、腹膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为薄而光滑的浆膜（）",
            "B.分前层和后层",
            "C.腹盆腔内各脏器的表面几乎均被腹膜覆盖",
            "D.具有分泌和吸收功能（）",
            "E.可形成系膜、网膜及韧带等结构"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ADE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 75
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1967、腹膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为薄而光滑的浆膜（）",
            "B.分壁层和脏层",
            "C.腹盆腔内各脏器的表面几乎均被腹膜覆盖",
            "D.具有分泌和吸收功能（）",
            "E.可形成系膜、网膜及韧带等结构"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 76
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1968、腹膜腔 （  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.由腹膜脏层和壁层围成",
            "B.男性腹膜腔密闭",
            "C.女性腹膜腔与外界可间接相通",
            "D.腹膜腔与腹腔在解剖学上为同一概念",
            "E.腹腔内的脏器均位于腹膜腔内"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 77
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1969、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.回肠",
            "B.卵巢",
            "C.空肠",
            "D.膀胱",
            "E.肾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 78
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1970、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.脾",
            "C.空肠",
            "D.降结肠",
            "E.阑尾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BCE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 79
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1971、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.空肠",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.子宫",
            "E.胃"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ACD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 80
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1972、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.子宫",
            "B.升结肠",
            "C.乙状结肠",
            "D.膀胱",
            "E.肾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 81
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1973、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肾",
            "B.肾上腺",
            "C.胰",
            "D.胃",
            "E.肝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 82
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1974、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.降结肠",
            "B.胃",
            "C.膀胱",
            "D.输尿管",
            "E.胰"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "DE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 83
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1975、小网膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为双层腹膜形成的结构",
            "B.连于肝与胃大弯及十二指肠上部之间",
            "C.左侧部为肝胃韧带",
            "D.右侧部为肝十二指肠韧带",
            "E.右侧缘游离缘后方有网膜孔"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ACDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 84
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1976、大网膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.形似围裙",
            "B.覆于空、回肠及横结肠的前方",
            "C.内有巨噬细胞",
            "D.有重要防御功能",
            "E.小儿大网膜较短"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABCDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 85
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1977、网膜囊（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.在小网膜、胃前壁与腹后壁腹膜之间",
            "B.位置较浅",
            "C.为腹膜腔的一部分",
            "D.经网膜孔通腹膜腔的其余部分",
            "E.除网膜孔外，网膜囊另有通道与腹膜腔其余部分相通"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "CD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 86
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1978、具有系膜的肠管（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠",
            "B.降结肠",
            "C.升结肠",
            "D.乙状结肠",
            "E.空肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ADE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 87
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1979、没有系膜的肠管是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.回肠",
            "B.空肠",
            "C.十二指肠",
            "D.降结肠",
            "E.阑尾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "CD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 88
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1980、直立位腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.直肠膀胱陷凹（男）",
            "B.膀胱子宫陷凹（女）",
            "C.直肠子宫陷凹（女）",
            "D.肝肾隐窝",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "AC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 89
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1981、肝十二韧带内重要结构排列是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.胆总管",
            "B.肝门静脉",
            "C.肝固有动脉",
            "D.肝总管",
            "E.肝静脉"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 90
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1982、Which of the following organs are retroperitoneal viscera (腹膜外位器官)?",
        "options": [
            "A.spleen",
            "B.kidney",
            "C.pancreas",
            "D.urinary bladder",
            "E.ureter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BCE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 91
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1983、Which of the following organs are intraperitoneal viscera (腹膜内位器官)?",
        "options": [
            "A.stomach",
            "B.gallbladder",
            "C.pancreas",
            "D.transverse colon",
            "E.liver"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "AD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 92
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1984、Which of the following organs are interperitoneal viscera (腹膜间位器官)?",
        "options": [
            "A.uterine tube",
            "B.jejunum",
            "C.ascending colon",
            "D.uterus",
            "E.urinary bladder"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "CDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 93
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1985、Which of the following organs are retroperitoneal viscera?",
        "options": [
            "A.kidney",
            "B.suprarenal gland",
            "C.uterus",
            "D.pancreas",
            "E.ureter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 94
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1986、The lesser omentum (小网膜) can be divided into which of following parts?",
        "options": [
            "A.gastrocolic ligament (胃结肠韧带)",
            "B.hepatogastric ligament (肝胃韧带)",
            "C.falciform ligament (镰状韧带)",
            "D.coronary ligament (冠状韧带)",
            "E.hepatoduodenal ligament (肝十二指肠韧带)"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 95
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1987、Which of the following ligaments are connected with the liver?",
        "options": [
            "A.round ligament of liver (肝圆韧带)",
            "B.hepatogastric ligament",
            "C.falciform ligament",
            "D.coronary ligament",
            "E.hepatoduodinal ligament"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABCDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 96
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1988、Which of the following ligaments are connected with the stomach?",
        "options": [
            "A.gastrosplenic ligament (胃脾韧带)",
            "B.hepatogastric ligament",
            "C.gastrocolic ligament (胃结肠韧带)",
            "D.gastrophrenic ligament (胃膈韧带)",
            "E.hepatoduodinal ligament"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABCD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 97
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1989、Which of the following ligaments are connected with the spleen?",
        "options": [
            "A.gastrosplenic ligament",
            "B.splenorenal ligament (脾肾韧带)",
            "C.gastrocolic ligament",
            "D.gastrophrenic ligament",
            "E.phrenicosplenic ligament (膈脾韧带)"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 98
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1990、Which of the following structures are located within the hepatoduodenal ligament?",
        "options": [
            "A.hepatic vein",
            "B.proper hepatic artery (肝固有动脉)",
            "C.common bile duct",
            "D.hepatic portal vein",
            "E.inferior vena cava"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BCD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 99
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1991、About the recess and pouch in peritoneum, which of the following discreption is correct?",
        "options": [
            "A.The hepatorenal recess is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position.",
            "B.In female, the rectouterine pouch is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position.",
            "C.In female, the vesicouterine pouch is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position.",
            "D.The hatatorenal recess is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in sitting position.",
            "E.In male, the rectovesical pouch is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position."
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 100
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1966、腹膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为薄而光滑的浆膜（）",
            "B.分前层和后层",
            "C.腹盆腔内各脏器的表面几乎均被腹膜覆盖",
            "D.具有分泌和吸收功能（）",
            "E.可形成系膜、网膜及韧带等结构"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ADE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 101
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1967、腹膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为薄而光滑的浆膜（）",
            "B.分壁层和脏层",
            "C.腹盆腔内各脏器的表面几乎均被腹膜覆盖",
            "D.具有分泌和吸收功能（）",
            "E.可形成系膜、网膜及韧带等结构"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 102
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1968、腹膜腔 （  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.由腹膜脏层和壁层围成",
            "B.男性腹膜腔密闭",
            "C.女性腹膜腔与外界可间接相通",
            "D.腹膜腔与腹腔在解剖学上为同一概念",
            "E.腹腔内的脏器均位于腹膜腔内"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 103
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1969、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.回肠",
            "B.卵巢",
            "C.空肠",
            "D.膀胱",
            "E.肾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 104
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1970、属腹膜内位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.脾",
            "C.空肠",
            "D.降结肠",
            "E.阑尾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BCE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 105
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1971、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肝",
            "B.空肠",
            "C.胆囊",
            "D.子宫",
            "E.胃"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ACD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 106
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1972、属腹膜间位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.子宫",
            "B.升结肠",
            "C.乙状结肠",
            "D.膀胱",
            "E.肾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 107
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1973、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.肾",
            "B.肾上腺",
            "C.胰",
            "D.胃",
            "E.肝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 108
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1974、属腹膜外位器官的是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.降结肠",
            "B.胃",
            "C.膀胱",
            "D.输尿管",
            "E.胰"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "DE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 109
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1975、小网膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.为双层腹膜形成的结构",
            "B.连于肝与胃大弯及十二指肠上部之间",
            "C.左侧部为肝胃韧带",
            "D.右侧部为肝十二指肠韧带",
            "E.右侧缘游离缘后方有网膜孔"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ACDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 110
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1976、大网膜（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.形似围裙",
            "B.覆于空、回肠及横结肠的前方",
            "C.内有巨噬细胞",
            "D.有重要防御功能",
            "E.小儿大网膜较短"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABCDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 111
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1977、网膜囊（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.在小网膜、胃前壁与腹后壁腹膜之间",
            "B.位置较浅",
            "C.为腹膜腔的一部分",
            "D.经网膜孔通腹膜腔的其余部分",
            "E.除网膜孔外，网膜囊另有通道与腹膜腔其余部分相通"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "CD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 112
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1978、具有系膜的肠管（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.横结肠",
            "B.降结肠",
            "C.升结肠",
            "D.乙状结肠",
            "E.空肠"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ADE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 113
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1979、没有系膜的肠管是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.回肠",
            "B.空肠",
            "C.十二指肠",
            "D.降结肠",
            "E.阑尾"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "CD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 114
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1980、直立位腹膜腔最低处（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.直肠膀胱陷凹（男）",
            "B.膀胱子宫陷凹（女）",
            "C.直肠子宫陷凹（女）",
            "D.肝肾隐窝",
            "E.盲肠后隐窝"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "AC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 115
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1981、肝十二韧带内重要结构排列是（  ）",
        "options": [
            "A.胆总管",
            "B.肝门静脉",
            "C.肝固有动脉",
            "D.肝总管",
            "E.肝静脉"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABC",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 116
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1982、Which of the following organs are retroperitoneal viscera (腹膜外位器官)?",
        "options": [
            "A.spleen",
            "B.kidney",
            "C.pancreas",
            "D.urinary bladder",
            "E.ureter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BCE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 117
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1983、Which of the following organs are intraperitoneal viscera (腹膜内位器官)?",
        "options": [
            "A.stomach",
            "B.gallbladder",
            "C.pancreas",
            "D.transverse colon",
            "E.liver"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "AD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 118
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1984、Which of the following organs are interperitoneal viscera (腹膜间位器官)?",
        "options": [
            "A.uterine tube",
            "B.jejunum",
            "C.ascending colon",
            "D.uterus",
            "E.urinary bladder"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "CDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 119
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1985、Which of the following organs are retroperitoneal viscera?",
        "options": [
            "A.kidney",
            "B.suprarenal gland",
            "C.uterus",
            "D.pancreas",
            "E.ureter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 120
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1986、The lesser omentum (小网膜) can be divided into which of following parts?",
        "options": [
            "A.gastrocolic ligament (胃结肠韧带)",
            "B.hepatogastric ligament (肝胃韧带)",
            "C.falciform ligament (镰状韧带)",
            "D.coronary ligament (冠状韧带)",
            "E.hepatoduodenal ligament (肝十二指肠韧带)"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 121
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1987、Which of the following ligaments are connected with the liver?",
        "options": [
            "A.round ligament of liver (肝圆韧带)",
            "B.hepatogastric ligament",
            "C.falciform ligament",
            "D.coronary ligament",
            "E.hepatoduodinal ligament"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABCDE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 122
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1988、Which of the following ligaments are connected with the stomach?",
        "options": [
            "A.gastrosplenic ligament (胃脾韧带)",
            "B.hepatogastric ligament",
            "C.gastrocolic ligament (胃结肠韧带)",
            "D.gastrophrenic ligament (胃膈韧带)",
            "E.hepatoduodinal ligament"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABCD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 123
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1989、Which of the following ligaments are connected with the spleen?",
        "options": [
            "A.gastrosplenic ligament",
            "B.splenorenal ligament (脾肾韧带)",
            "C.gastrocolic ligament",
            "D.gastrophrenic ligament",
            "E.phrenicosplenic ligament (膈脾韧带)"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ABE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 124
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1990、Which of the following structures are located within the hepatoduodenal ligament?",
        "options": [
            "A.hepatic vein",
            "B.proper hepatic artery (肝固有动脉)",
            "C.common bile duct",
            "D.hepatic portal vein",
            "E.inferior vena cava"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BCD",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 125
    },
    {
        "question_text": "1991、About the recess and pouch in peritoneum, which of the following discreption is correct?",
        "options": [
            "A.The hepatorenal recess is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position.",
            "B.In female, the rectouterine pouch is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position.",
            "C.In female, the vesicouterine pouch is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position.",
            "D.The hatatorenal recess is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in sitting position.",
            "E.In male, the rectovesical pouch is the lowest part of the peritoneal cavity in erect position."
        ],
        "correct_answer": "BE",
        "analysis": "暂无解析",
        "total_number": "126",
        "number": 126
    }
]